netvoyage.com 2018-10-04

# Privacy Policy

NetDocuments Software, Inc. is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy by developing and deploying technology which gives you a powerful and safe online experience.  This policy outlines what we do to meet those commitments.

**Differentiating Between the NetDocuments Service and the NetDocuments Website.**  The website [www.netdocuments.com](http://www.netdocuments.com/) is provided as a means to convey information to you about the NetDocuments Service. The website contains literature, demos, company information, etc. From the [www.netdocuments.com](http://www.netdocuments.com/) site, you can choose to opt-in to receive literature and information which will be used to communicate with you related to your interest.

Once you register for the NetDocuments Service, you can access the NetDocuments Service directly via the link provided when you registered, for example, [https://vault.netvoyage.com](https://vault.netvoyage.com/), bypassing the [www.netdocuments.com](http://www.netdocuments.com/) site, if you choose. All personally identifiable information collected to create your account is stored under your account within the Service and can be changed by you at any time by logging into the NetDocuments Service, selecting Settings, and Personal Information. To delete your account see the "Access Your Account and Your Personal Information" section of this policy.

**NetDocuments Service.**   NetDocuments provides a highly-secure, Cloud-based, multi-tenant, Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) Document Management Service (DMS or "Service") to its customers.  As a SaaS DMS provider, NetDocuments is responsible for protecting the privacy of Personally Identifiable Information (PII) it gathers from its customers to create and maintain Service accounts, referred to in this policy as "customer PII."  NetDocuments is also responsible for the privacy of data which customers of NetDocuments place in the customer DMS data repositories, referred to as "customer data" and "Customer Data Files" or "CDFs."

**Protecting Personally Identifiable Information.**   In matters related to how customer PII is used and maintained, NetDocuments agrees to be subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Department of Commerce, the Federal Trade Commission (FTC), the Department of Transportation, or any other U.S. authorized statutory body as applicable.  If there is an incident related to customer PII, NetDocuments accepts the possibility, under certain conditions, for the customer to invoke binding arbitration.  Customer need to know that NetDocuments may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.  NetDocuments may, depending on the circumstances, have liability in any cases of onward transfers of customer PII to third parties.

NetDocuments complies with the **U.S. - E.U.   Privacy Shield** Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. NetDocuments has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles.  If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov.

If you have questions or concerns about how your Personally Identifiable Information may be used by NetDocuments, you may contact our Compliance Department by sending an email to compliance@netdocuments.com or by telephoning 866-NET-DOCS (866-638-3627).  If you believe your PII has been inappropriately used, in addition to contacting NetDocuments directly, you may also open a formal, independent Privacy Shield case at https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield.

NetDocuments has further committed to cooperate with the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning human resources data transferred from the EU in the context of the employment relationship.  If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from NetDocuments, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact the EU DPAs for more information or to file a complaint.  The services of the EU DPAs are provided at no cost to you.

NetDocuments also complies with the  **U.S. - Swiss  Privacy Shield** Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information transferred from Switzerland to the United States. NetDocuments has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the U.S. – Swiss Privacy Shield Principles.  If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).  If you have questions or concerns about how your Personally Identifiable Information may be used by NetDocuments, you may contact our Compliance Department by sending an email to compliance@netdocuments.com or by telephoning 866-NET-DOCS (866-638-3627).  If you believe your PII has been inappropriately used, in addition to contacting NetDocuments directly, you may also open a formal, independent Privacy Shield case at https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield

**Personally Identifiable Information Collected.**  No information that can uniquely identify an individual is gathered by merely visiting the www.netdocuments.com   website. Personally identifiable information is only collected when you are registered for a NetDocuments Service account.  This information gathered to create a service account is as follows:

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Organization name
  * Credit card information (Credit card information for the subscribing organization is collected using SSL encrypted pages and is only required when services are purchased. Credit card information is not stored online)

**Use of Personally Identifiable Information.**  We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone, except as described in this privacy policy (see "Business Transitions" below). We may share personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:

  1. Verification services need to do credit card checks, etc.
  2. We find that your actions on our web sites violate the Terms of Use.
  3. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process serviced on our Web site.

We do not share information with any third parties for their own marketing purposes.

Within the NetDocuments Service, only other registered users can view your name, email, telephone, organization, etc. to assist them in identification for the purpose of sharing documents with you.

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. _To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at  _[https://support.netdocuments.com](https://support.netdocuments.com/). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements.  With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name.  If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [https://support.netdocuments.com](https://support.netdocuments.com/). 

**Opt-Out Options** NetDocuments is required to offer individuals the opportunity to choose (opt-out) whether their personal information is (i) to be disclosed to a third party or (ii) to be used for a purpose that is materially different from the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individuals.  If an individual desires to opt out of having their personally identifiable information used in the ways described in this policy, or in any subsequent manner proposed by NetDocuments, that individual may contact NetDocuments at [https://support.netdocuments.com](https://support.netdocuments.com/) and request to have the individual’s personally identifiable information removed or not used as appropriate to the situation.  Individuals may also contact the NetDocuments Compliance Department at [compliance@netdocuments.com](mailto:compliance@netdocuments.com) to initiate or ensure any opt-out request.

**Privacy Obligations Regarding Customer Data Files within the NetDocuments DMS.**

All data files which a customer uploads into the NetDocuments Service or creates within the Service remain the property of the customer.  NetDocuments is only a custodian for the customer data files.  All customer data files are encrypted in transit and at rest and are safely stored in highly secure data centers.  The customer controls all access to and use of the customer data files.  NetDocuments personnel have no access to customer data files except when explicitly granted by the customer.  NetDocuments has no knowledge regarding the content of customer data files.  This means customers assume responsibility for meeting Privacy Shield obligations and any other obligations or restrictions for how customer data files are used.  NetDocuments' responsibility is to provide a robust, highly secure DMS for its customers.

Within the DMS, your Documents are protected with industry-leading security. If you are a registered user of the NetDocuments Service our security system ensures that no one can access your documents except those with whom you choose to share them, which may include other employees or associates of your company, and your DMS Administrators. The NetDocuments Service has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information provided to the Service. The DMS servers are maintained in secure, safe, trusted and audited environments. Credit card information for the subscribing organization is collected using SSL encrypted pages and is only required when services are purchased. Credit card information is not stored online.

If you have questions or concerns about how customer data files may be stored by NetDocuments, you may contact our Compliance Department by sending an email to compliance@netdocuments.com or by telephoning 866-NET-DOCS (866-638-3627).

**Tracking Technologies**. NetDocuments uses session ID cookies on this website.  A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes.  We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. The NetDocuments session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. If you reject session ID cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. Some of our business partners (such as a web analytics company) use cookies and clear gifs on our site. We have no access to or control over these third party technologies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by NetDocuments only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.

When logging into the NetDocuments Service, we also create a per-session cookie, which is maintained when using the NetDocuments Service for identification purposes. If you do not allow per-session cookies with your browser, then your usage of the NetDocuments Service is disallowed.

From within the NetDocuments Service, another user can register you within the Service, if you are not already registered, so as to share documents with you. When this occurs, you can choose not to accept the Terms of Use and this associated Privacy Policy by not clicking on the link contained in the welcome email. In this case, your account will remain inactive. Once you have logged in, you can opt-out of receiving notifications of events and special offers by removing the flag in Settings, Personal Information at any time thereafter. You can also change other personal information stored in Settings.

When you create an account on our Online Community to post comments we ask for your name and email address. We use this information to identify community users and monitor comments. If you use our community site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums and community sites, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums or other community sites.

**Communications from the NetDocuments Website**. If you have not opted-out of receiving mailings, we will communicate with you (generally by email, website, or Help documentation) to update NetDocuments Service information, provide support, request feedback, provide marketing and service information, request marketing input, and provide special offers and incentives related to NetDocuments. We may post feedback comments from users as anonymous comments on our Web page. Non-identifiable, aggregate information may be shared with interested parties. If you have opted-out of receiving these mailings, your only avenue of information regarding the NetDocuments Service will be via the Terms of Use Agreement, a message on the Login page of the NetDocuments Service, or on the [www.netdocuments.com](http://www.netdocuments.com/) website.

When you register you have the opportunity to opt-in to these mailings. You also have the ability to opt-out at a later time by adjusting your Account Information, while you are logged into the NetDocuments Service. You may also unsubscribe from promotional emails by following our unsubscribe instructions included in each email.

**Access Your Account and Your Personal Information.**  To change personal information in your Service account, log into the NetDocuments Service, go to Settings, and select Personal Information.  You may change the personal information in your account at any time. The personal information is used by others to identify you when sharing documents with you.

If you would like to delete your Account, you may contact your NetDocuments repository administrator within your company to remove you from the repository. If you are the administrator and would like to cancel and delete your NetDocuments service, or if you wish to delete your account from any of the NetDocuments online community websites (including the Support or Developer sites), contact NetDocuments support ([https://support.netdocuments.com](https://support.netdocuments.com/)) and request that your name be deleted from these sites. We will respond to all requests regarding access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

When you contact us via links on our site, your email address and information is kept only for the purposes of responding to your request and future requests that you may have. If you contact us via support, any information you provide may be used to respond and resolve your questions or issues. This also applies to posts on the NetDocuments Forum pages.

**Links to Other Sites.**  The Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by NetDocuments. Please be aware that we, NetDocuments, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

**Social Media Widgets.** Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Single Sign-On**. You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form.  Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

**Business Transitions.**  In the event NetDocuments Software, Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via a prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement.**  If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective.

NetDocuments Customer Support: [https://support.netdocuments.com](https://support.netdocuments.com/)

NetDocuments  
2500 W Executive Pkwy Suite 350  
Lehi, UT 84043  
801.226.6882

Last Updated May, 2018  
Copyright © 2001-2018 NetDocuments Software, Inc. All rights reserved.
